



Stróża, woj. lubelskie



piotr.kijewski@gmail.com



664 414 737



piotr-kijewski

Skills

Teamwork

Problem solving

Organization and planning of work

Languages

English B1

SOFTWARE

TestLink, Jira,
Postman, SQL,
Microsoft Windows, Office
Android

PIOTR KIJEWSKI

Professional summary

I worked as a person responsible for verifying the quality of products in industries such as energy, automotive and aviation. I used various types of measuring instruments for this, including Coordinate Measuring Machines.

I value team work. I easily adjust the organization and working time to the specifics and conditions of the project.

In order to further develop my competences, I changed my profession to IT, while remaining in the quality control department, because I feel at home in it, which is confirmed by my many years of experience.

Work history

PPW NABOR 04.2014 – 02.2022

Senior quality control specialist (06.2021-02.2022)

Quality control specialist (04.2017-06.2021)

Mechanical Engineer (04.2014-03.2017)

Control of products and instrumentation with the use of CMM, delivery control, supervision over control and measuring instruments.

Ability to read and interpret standards as well as read and analyze technical documentation. Development of documents and instructions based on customer requirements, issuing measurement reports, quality certificates, FAI reports.

Participation in projects related to the introduction and launch of new products.

Thoni Alutec Sp. z o.o. 07.2012 – 03.2014

Quality controller in the R&D Centre

Operation of measuring machines and devices, visual inspection, keeping quality documentation, making decisions about conforming or non-conforming products, making decisions regarding the suspension of the production process.

Military University of Technology 03.2010 - 06.2012

Senior technician (06.2010 – 06.2012)

Technician (03.2010 – 06.2010)

Maintaining the technical efficiency of the equipment assigned to service (including aircraft), financial responsibility for the entrusted equipment and property, performing tests and measurements in the construction laboratory.

Aviation Service Company "Heliseco" Sp. z o.o. 07.2009 – 02.2010

Specialist in the operation and planning of aircraft equipment maintenance *Planning and monitoring of aircraft operation and repair.*

Education

Lublin University of Technology 10.2004 – 03.2010

Field of study: Mechanics and Machine Design Specialization: Construction of helicopters Obtained title: Master of Science in Engineering

Certificates

ISTQB® Certified Tester - Foundation Level (03.2022)

Courses and training

ISTQB® Certified Tester - Foundation Level (12.2021)
Practical software testing course – Udemy (01.2022)

Hobby

Smart devices, mechanics, board games,

I agree to the processing of personal data provided in this document for realising the recruitment process pursuant to the Personal Data Protection Act of 10 May 2018 (Journal of Laws 2018, item 1000) and in agreement with Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation).